[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Major League Baseball pitcher was nicknamed, The Spaceman?", "correct_answer": "Bill Lee", "incorrect_answers": ["Dennis Rodman", "Bill Romanowski", "Mark Fidrytch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the previous name of the Los Angeles Dodgers?", "correct_answer": "The Brooklyn Dodgers", "incorrect_answers": ["The Kansas City Dodgers", "The Bronx Dodgers", "The Baltimore Dodgers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The botanical term bonsai, deriving from Japanese, refers to which of these?", "correct_answer": "A technique for miniature growing trees", "incorrect_answers": ["A species of miniature trees", "A type of fertilizer that reduces the size of trees", "A region in Japan where miniature trees grow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first person to fly a balloon that was filled with hydrogen gas?", "correct_answer": "Jacques A.C. Charles", "incorrect_answers": ["Count Ferdinand Zeppelin", "Francois F. DeRozier", "Joseph Montgolier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which chinchilla species do most of the domestic chinchillas belong?", "correct_answer": "Chinchilla lanigera", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Giant Chinchilla", "Chinchilla brevicaudata"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word dinosaur is a combination of two Greek words. One word  means lizard. What does the other word mean?", "correct_answer": "Terrifying", "incorrect_answers": ["Herbivorous", "Godlike", "Beautiful"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these toys is seen in Chandler and Joeys apartment on the TV show Friends?", "correct_answer": "Magna Doodle", "incorrect_answers": ["Silly Puty", "LEGO Building Blocks", "Draughts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was not a member of the Average Joes Gymnasium dodgeball team featured in the movie Dodgeball?", "correct_answer": "Fran, the female Romanovian dodgeball champion", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve, the pirate", "Gordon, a subscriber to Obscure Sports Quarterly magazine", "Justin, a high school male cheerleader"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This trio of talented ladies starred in the 2000 movie Chocolat.", "correct_answer": "Juliette Binoche, Lena Olin, Judi Dench", "incorrect_answers": ["Kathy Bates, Sharon Stone, Carrie-Anne Moss", "Cher, Susan Sarandon, Julia Roberts", "Kate Blanchet, Judi Dench, Juliette Binoche"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following was not a game show host?", "correct_answer": "Walter Bradley", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Allen", "Chuck Barris", "Louie Anderson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 1994 movie, directed by Robert Zemeckis, in which the main character compared life to a box of chocolates.", "correct_answer": "\u2018Forrest Gump\u2019", "incorrect_answers": ["What Lies Beneath", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "Cast Away"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first frost will come within this many days, after you hear the first cicada.", "correct_answer": "90", "incorrect_answers": ["45", "50", "60"]}]